Finding Aid for Suomi College Finnish-American collection, 1880-1972
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Finnish-American Collection: Church Records, Labor Societies, Temperance Organizations, and others
  - Temperance Society Nuorison Kaunistus [The Beauty of the Youth], Redridge, Michigan
    - Minute book
      - November 6, 1904-February 4, 1906 (Reel 100)
The Archive of Mr. Alex Kyyhkynen (Duluth, Minnesota), the former Honorary Consul of Finland, Reels 30 and 31
The Archives of Rev. Arvi Henri Saarisuu (Crystal Falls, Mich.), Reel 5
Athletic Club Oma Voima [Self Power], Monessen, Pa., Reel 22
The Illness Aid Organization of Monessen, Penn., Reel 55
The Finnish-American Historical Society of Iron County, Mich., Reel 62
Finnish-Athletic Club Tarmo ja Huima [Energy and Hotspur] South Range, Mich., Reel 71
Finnish Club of Quincy, Mass., Reel 43
Finnish Illness and Accident Aid Association (Hancock, Mich.), Reel 76
Finnish Lutheran Publishing Company (Hancock, Mich.), Reel 100
The Finnish National Committee of De Kalb, Illinois, Reel 70
Help Finland Committee of Troy, N.H., Reel 77
Help Finland Materials (to help Finland during the Second World War), Reel 70, 72
Help Finland Materials from Mich. (during the Second World War), Reels 54 and 55
Kalevan Ritarit [The Knights of Kaleva], Fitchburg, Mass., Reel 48
Kansanvalistusseura [Popular Educational Society], Calumet, Mich., Reel 97
Lännen Lähtysliitto [The Mission League of the West], Astoria, Oregon, Reel 62
Materials on Suomi College, Hancock, Mich., Reel 97
Musical Society Sibelius Club (Monessen, Penn.), Reel 22